Guide to the Raymond Germann Photograph Collection 1978-2016 PR 311
New-York Historical Society
Raymond Germann Photograph Collection
ca. 1978-2016
2005-2014
New-York Historical Society
PR 311
9 Linear feet (6 boxes)
The Raymond Germann Photograph Collection consists of over 300 archival inkjet photographs of New York City street scenes taken between 1978-2016. Four are color prints, the remainder are black and white prints.
Scope and Contents note
The Raymond Germann Photograph Collection consists of 378 archival inkjet photographs of New York City, taken between 1978 and 2016. The images are street scenes, many featuring billboards, advertising, store fronts, murals, street fairs and street vendors. The photos are mainly of Manhattan, including Greenwich Village, Harlem, Washington Heights, the High Line, lower Manhattan and midtown. There are also a few images of Brooklyn, the Bronx and Queens, including 2 color prints of graffiti at the 5 Pointz Building in Long Island City. The images were numbered by the photographer; titles are based on photographer's identification.
Note: the prints are numbered; There is NO print # 177, and NO prints #340-360.
Access Restrictions
Available by advance appointment only. To schedule an appointment, contact the Print Room Librarian at printroom@nyhistory.org.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to 20 exposures of stable, unbound material per day. Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.
Provenance
This collection was a gift from the photographer, 2013, 2014, 2015 & 2016.
- [1] Theater District, 7th Avenue and West 48th Street, 2011; 1 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [2] Woman with dogs, Park Avenue, 1981; 2 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [3] Battery Park, iron railing, 2011; 3 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [4] Ninth Avenue International Food Festival, looking north, 1982; 4 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [5] The Music Inn, Bleecker Street, Greenwich Village, 2011; 5 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [6] 9th Avenue, midtown, man with flag, 1982 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [7] Citicorp buildings, Lexington Avenue, 53rd Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [8] The High Line, line in parking area, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
- [9] Eyes, 10th Avenue, Chelsea, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [10] Mural, Greenpoint, Brooklyn, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [11] Mural, Houston Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [12] Park Sign, Broadway, Lower Manhattan, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [13] 10th Avenue, window, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [14] Sign with Cher's picture, Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [15] Guitars for sale, 6th Avenue, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [16] Cheese shop, 3rd Avenue between 9th Street and Bowery, East Village, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
- [17] Vitra Store, 9th Avenue near 14th Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [18] The High Line, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [19] Mural, Chelsea, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [20] Festival, 6th Avenue, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [21] Line buildings, 47th Street and Broadway, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [22] Chevy's Signs, 8th Avenue at 42nd Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [23] Brooklyn Bridge taken from Pearl Street, 1980 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [24] Houston Street mural, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
- [25] Vendor, Broadway and West 177th Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [26] Soho, around Greene Street and Houston Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [27] Pick up truck with flags, Broadway, lower Manhattan, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [28] Chinatown, Grand Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [29] Beauty shop sign, Harlem, 125th Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [30] Sign, Weehawken Street near Christopher Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [31] Dior store renovation, East 57th Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [32] Cartier Bresson exhibition sign, Houston Street near 6th Avenue, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
- [33] Optical Eye, Avenue A, East Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [34] Thai Restaurant, Greenwich Avenue, Greenwich Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [35] Italian Hero sign, delicatessen, 8th Avenue near 14th Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [36] Paul's Hamburger, 2nd Avenue and St. Mark's Place, East Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [37] Chairs in window, Greenwich Avenue, Greenwich Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [38] Four women mannequins, St. Nicholas Avenue, Washington Heights, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [39] Clocks, Washington Square Festival, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
- [40] Census sign, Union Square, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [41] Battery Park, Service Men and Women Memorial, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [42] Hot dog stand, West 53rd Street across from MOMA, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [43] Grand Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [44] Doors with the word "colors" on them, Lafayette Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [45] Sephora sign, 42nd Street near 7th Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [46] Washington Heights, 178th Street, George Washington Bridge in background, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [47] Moondance Diner, 6th Avenue near Spring Street, ca. 1988 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
- [48] Lincoln Center Plaza, 2011 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [49] Sign with faces and fence, 7th Avenue and Greenwich Avenue, 2007 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [50] Ice floats, Hudson River near 42nd Street, 2003 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [51] Fish Lure, Fulton Street, South Street Seaport, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [52] Bill's Flower Shop, 6th Avenue at 32nd Street, 1990 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [53] Woman at bus stop, West 57th Street, 1986 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [54] Security guard, 7th Avenue near 50th Street, 1988 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [55] Porta Bello sign, 125th Street, Harlem, 2010 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
- [56] Lincoln Center, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [57] Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [58] Billboard, 42nd Street, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [59] Buildings collage, 6th Avenue, 2007 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [60] Battery Park, behind World Financial Center, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [61] Porto Rico Coffee store, Bleecker Street, Greenwich Village, 2009 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [62] Mannequins, St. Nicholas Avenue and 180th Street, 2005 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [63] Sneaker sign, 181st Street, Washington Heights, 2008 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
- [64] Viaduct, 12th Avenue at 125th Street, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [65] Holocaust Museum at Battery Park, 2008 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [66] Buoys, Hudson River, Chelsea, 2008 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [67] Chinese signs with numbers, Grand Street, Chinatown, 2008 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [68] Stoop with signs, Grand Street, Chinatown, 2008 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [69] Jewelry store window, 57th Street at 5th Avenue, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [70] Uncle Sam, 9th Avenue, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [71] Opera singer, West 57th Street in front of Carnegie Hall, 1993 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
- [72] Rape victim sign, 9th Avenue, 1993 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [73] Parking lot with small signs, near 6th Avenue and West 20th Street, ca. 1988 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [74] From the High Line, abstract signs, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [75] 11th Avenue car dealer, at 26th Street, Chelsea, 2005 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [76] Worth Street, park benches, n.d (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [77] Maxilla & Mandible anatomy store, 1990 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [78] The High Line, with billboard, 10th Avenue looking north, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [79] Beckenstein sign, Orchard Street, 2005 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
- [80] John Jovino gun shop, Grand Street, 2007 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [81] Oval shape with staircase, Washington Street, lower Manhattan, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [82] James Brown tribute sign, Frederick Douglass Blvd, Harlem near 127th Street, 2006 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [83] Buildings Collage, 6th Avenue from West 48th Street, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [84] The Lone Star Roadhouse bus, West 52nd Street near Broadway, 1992 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [85] S. Klein department store, Union Square and 14th Street, ca. 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [86] Airplane on building, Times Square, ca. 1990 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [87] Building with scribble lines, Broadway near Canal Street, ca. 1990 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
- [88] Wig Store, West 125th Street near St. Nicholas Avenue, Harlem, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [89] Panchitos, Minetta Lane, Greenwich Village, 1995 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [90] Abingdon Market, Eighth Avenue and Jane Street, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [91] Four faces on building, 14th Street and 2nd Avenue, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [92] Billboard with people, Broadway at 57th Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [93] Sculpture artist, sculptures for sale, 7th Avenue South, Greenwich Village, 1999 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [94] Ladies luncheon, 9th Avenue near 35th Street, 1988 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [95] Festival, 6th Avenue, Brazil t-shirts, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
- [96] Arrows, 6th Avenue at 43rd Street, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [97] Tree sculpture, Avenue A near Tompkins Square Park, 2003 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [98] Bed, Gansevoort Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [99] Coffee sign, Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [100] Ladies' underwear cart, St. Nicholas Avenue and 175th Street, Washington Heights, 2006 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [101] Optical store, Broome Street, 2008 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [102] Sculpture of men, West Broadway, Soho, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [103] Mannequins, Canal Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
- [104] Poster, Cedric, West 125th Street, Harlem, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [105] Daibo Trading Co., Hester Street, 2007 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [106] Chinatown signs, East Broadway, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [107] Greenwich Paints, Sixth Avenue(?), Greenwich Village, 1978 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [108] Habana Coffee sign, Prince Street and Elizabeth Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [109] Water Street plaza overlooking the East River, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [110] Door with decals and messages, Houston Street, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [111] Sign with moving gear and lettering, Houston Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
- [112] Casa Magazine store, 8th Avenue between 12th Street and Jane Street, West Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [113] One half woman mannequin, Houston Street, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [114] Metropolitan Museum, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [115] McDonald's sign, Broadway, midtown, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [116] Iguana Restaurant sign, West 54th Street and Broadway, 2011 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [117] Omega Oil signs, Frederick Douglass Blvd and West 147th Street, Harlem, 2003 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [118] Paris Signs, postcards and posters, Bleecker Street, 1999 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [119] Jean Claude Cafe, Sullivan Street between Houston and Prince Streets, 2010 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
- [120] Visiones, MacDougal Street and West 3rd Street, 1996 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [121] Manhattan Bridge, Brooklyn, 2004 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [122] Mural, East 9th Street, East Village, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [123] Tattoo Head, Tompkins Square Park, East Village, 2009 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [124] 9/11 Tribute tiles, 7th Avenue and Greenwich Avenue, 2007 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [125] Revelations Antiques, 2nd Avenue, East Village, 1995 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [126] St. Patrick's Cathedral, Fifth Avenue, 1979 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [127] Twin Towers from the Brooklyn Bridge, 1988 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
- [128] Park Signs, 10th Avenue and West 35th Street, 2003 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [129] Parade Truck, Madison Avenue near 106th Street, 2005 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [130] Yale Truck, West Side Highway and West 40th Street, 1990 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [131] Small boats, South Street Seaport, 1991 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [132] T-shirt store, St. Mark's Place, East Village, 2010 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [133] Street Fair, 6th Avenue, Greek food, 2010 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [134] Sign vendor, Pier 17, South Street Seaport, 2007 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [135] Wig Cart, St. Nicholas Avenue and West 173rd Street, Washington Heights, 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
- [136] Water Street garage, 1991 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [137] Todito Fashions, Broadway around West 173rd Street, Washington Heights, 1995 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [138] Shadows on sidewalk, Vesey Street and the West Side Highway, 1980 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [139] Political truck, West 178th Street, Washington Heights, ca. 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [140] Sutton Clock Shop, Lexington Avenue and East 62nd Street, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [141] Ezra Cohen Fabric sign, Grand Street, Lower East Side, 2005 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [142] Met Roof, Metropolitan Museum, 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [143] Obama poster on newsstand, Broadway near Union Square, 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
- [144] One World Trade Center (Freedom Tower) construction, from inside World Financial Center, West Side Highway, 2007 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [145] Tourneau Watch signs, East 57th Street and Madison Avenue, 2004 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [146] Hat Vendor, Orchard Street, 2000 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [147] Toy Vendor, Orchard Street, 2000 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [148] Faces on Wall, Eldridge and Stanton Streets, 1998 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [149] Teddy's Restaurant with Statue of Liberty crown, West Broadway, Tribeca, 1987 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [150] World Financial Center, West Side Highway, lower Manhattan, 1992 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [151] Ronald Reagan cut out, 6th Avenue and West 52nd Street, 1986 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
- [152] Going out of business sign, 5th Avenue, Midtown, 1996 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [153] Optical store with eyeglasses sign, Orchard Street, 2007 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [154] The Frankerie, fast food store, Broadway and West 61st Street, 1993 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [155] Pier 17, South Street Seaport, looking out at the Brooklyn Bridge, 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [156] Billboard of basketball player, Houston and Wooster Street, 1997 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [157] Municipal Building with the Brooklyn Bridge in background, 1980 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [158] Hub Cap Shop, Frederick Douglass Blvd., Harlem, ca. 2004 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [159] ATM machine, Orchard Street near Houston Street, 2007 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
- [160] Jussara Lee Fashions, Little West 12th Street near 9th Avenue, 2011 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [161] Miss Kitty, Reader and Advisor, 26 Dekalb Avenue, Brooklyn, 2010 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [162] Man handing out pamphlets, with dogs, Broadway near West 62nd Street, 1994 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [163] Man selling African art, West 53rd Street near MOMA, 1993 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [164] Variety store, St. Nicholas Avenue and West 180th Street, Washington Heights, 2005 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [165] Building with small signs on it, Bowery and Houston Street, 2011 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [166] Big Chair, Central Park at 59th Street, near 5th Avenue, 1999 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [167] Barbershop, MacDougal and Bleecker Streets, 1998 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
- [168] Bicycle made out of fabric, Greene Street near Canal Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [169] Freedom sign on building, Lispenard Street near Church Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [170] GI Joe and street vendor, South 6th Street near Bedford Avenue, Williamsburgh, Brooklyn, 2007 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [171] Brick building [Tobacco Warehouse] looking out to Brooklyn Bridge Park, DUMBO, Brooklyn, 2009 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [172] Brooklyn Bridge Park, view of Manhattan skyline from DUMBO Brooklyn, 2009 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [173] Elevated train tacks, Broadway near Crescent Street, Astoria, Queens, n.d. (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [174] Anti-fur demonstration, West 57th Street near Lexington Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [175] Hammacher Schlemmer store, East 57th Street near Lexington Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [176] Manhattan Bridge, from Washington Street, DUMBO, Brooklyn, 2008 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
- [178] Bernstein Deli Restaurant, 3rd Avenue and 70th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [179] Guggenheim Museum, 5th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [180] Wig on sign, 181st Street near Amsterdam Avenue, Washington Heights, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [181] Three mannequins, 6th Ave, Greenwich Village, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [182] Sammy's Restaurant sign, City Island Avenue, Bronx, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [183] MLB Sports Store, Broadway, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [184] Bath tub on building, 125th Street near 2nd Avenue, Harlem, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [185] Plaza, Battery Park, behind World Financial Center building, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
- [186] Leggings, street fair, Bleecker Street, Greenwich Village, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [187] Battery Park building, looking through opening, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [188] Religion protester, Washington Square, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [189] President Obama poster, Union Square, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [190] Louis Vitton store, East 57th Street and 5th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [191] Mural of sailor and woman, West 25th Street and 10th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [192] Bridal party, 10th Avenue at West 30th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [193] The Blue Store, clocks in window, 8th Avenue at West 21st Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
- [194] Girl with camera handbag, 6th Avenue, Greenwich Village, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [195] Pickle stand, street fair, Washington Square North, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [196] The Dragonmaster, man in costume, Central Park, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [197] Face along the High Line, from 10th Avenue at West 30th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [198] Woman's Fingers billboard, High Line, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [199] Hell's Angels headquarters, East 3rd Street between 1st and 2nd Avenues, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [200] Woolworth Building collage from South Street, below Brooklyn Bridge, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [201] Political truck, Broadway at West 177th Street, Washington Heights, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
- [202] Kaleidoscope painting on wall, Houston Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [203] Halstead Properties real estate sign, Broadway, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [204] Signs, Madison Street, Chinatown, vertical format, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [205] Signs, Madison Street, Chinatown, horizontal format, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [206] Brooklyn Bridge and beach from Pier 17, South Street Seaport, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [207] Stairway, Madison Street, Chinatown, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [208] Sign with cast of Dark Shadows, Houston Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [209] Elevated tracks, 125th Street, Harlem, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
- [210] Poster store, Mulberry and Grand Streets, Little Italy, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [211] White wall with symbols, Houston Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [212] Frameworks frame store, Great Jones Street and Lafayette, Noho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [213] Beckham billboard, 8th Avenue at 34th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [214] African American One Hour Framing store, Nassau Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [215] Radio 77 Hits sign, St. Nicholas Avenue and West 145th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [216] Chess pieces, Houston Street, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [217] Chinatown sign collage, Eldridge Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
- [218] Gertz Plaza Mall sign, Sutphin Boulevard, Jamaica, Queens, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [219] Ink and Toner store, Archer Avenue, Jamaica, Queens, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [220] Alex's Furniture store sign, Archer Avenue, Jamaica, Queens, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [221] Bulgari store with circles, 5th Avenue at 57th Street, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [222] Mural of two young men, Houston Street, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [223] Coffee cups on building sign, Barclay Street, Lower Manhattan, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [224] Mannequin in two pieces, Houston Street, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [225] Mt. Zion Lutheran Church sign, West 145th Street and Convent Avenue, Washington Heights, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
- [226] Sign announcing exhibit at Jewish Museum, Houston Street, Soho, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [227] Two women with walkers, West 25th Street near 10th Avenue, Chelsea, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [228] Cats & Dogs painting on building, 103rd Street and 3rd Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [229] Paintings of musicians on building, West 125th Street and 12th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [230] Watch store and posters, East 57th Street near 5th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [231] Chemist store with advertisement posters, East 57th Street near 5th Avenue, 2012 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [232] Rags-a-Go-Go Vintage Clothing, West 14th Street between 7th and 8th Avenues, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [233] Mannequins in windows, 5th Avenue near West 52nd Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
- [234] Remi Hair and Wig store, Broadway and West 30th Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [235] Sign collage, West 32nd Street and 6th Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [236] E & L Sportswear, West 14th Street between 6th and 7th Avenues, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [237] Sin girls, Washington Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [238] Rooftops, South Street Seaport, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [239] Locks, Mott Street below Canal Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [240] Martian on wall, parking lot, Mulberry Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [241] Two faces on wall, Mott Street and Houston Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
- [242] Stuyvesant Park, street fair, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [243] Manhattan skyline and pilings from Brooklyn Bridge Park, Brooklyn, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [244] Yuban Coffee factory building, Courtyard and Brooklyn Bridge, DUMBO, Brooklyn, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [245] Street fair with large gorilla foot, Broadway at West 72nd Street, 1993 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [246] ATM man, Times Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [247] Window portraits, 5th Avenue, Midtown, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [248] Eye sign in window, East 28th Street and Lexington Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [249] Two doors with posters, Broadway and West 175th Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
- [250] Mural on side of building, East 35th Street and 6th Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [251] Door with Third Avenue lettering, 3rd Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [252] Native American sculpture on wall, 5th Avenue and East 45th Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [253] Women talking with woman figure looking at them, 5th Avenue, Midtown, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [254] Painting of woman on side of building, West 24th Street and 10th Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)